The industrial building we're visiting today
is allegedly a popular spot for suicide.
Honey...you're finally home.
I'm glad you're OK. You scared me to death.
You should have told me when you
went into hiding.
You fell off the grid all of a sudden.
Those loan sharks are after me every day.
Thanks, Pops.
Must have been tough for you.
I'll pay them back.
You? You have money?
You have money to spare?
Wow! So much money...
You scared me to death. What do you want?
Are the loan sharks after you?
Worse than loan sharks.
Sit down...come in.
Uncle, you went to the Police
and suddenly think Sylvia is dead.
Is it because...Sylvia appeared
in your dream?
Of course there's more.
When I dreamt of her, I felt very uneasy.
I texted her
but someone else texted back.
Look, Sylvia called me "Dad",
but she aways calls me "Pops".
I asked her about things of the past
hoping to sound her out.
I asked her the name of the dog we had,
when she was little,
she didn't remember.
It was so long ago, maybe she forgot.
Sylvia had asthma when she was little.
We never had a dog.
I confronted her right away
and asked her why she was posing
as my daughter.
She flipped out
and blocked my calls afterwards.
But Uncle, during this time,
Sylvia continued to upload new videos
and livestream.
It wasn't her.
Look.
Wow, thanks for the
"I love Siu Yiu" amethyst.
I love you too.
This Sylvia's voice is stiff
and she's not moving.
Don't you find that strange at all?
Well? Looking for me?
Yes...Yau You-fong gave us a new lead.
He pointed out something weird about
Siu Zi-yiu's livestreaming
these past two weeks.
New one on this side, old one over there.
Her facial expression is very stiff.
TCD colleagues analyzed the source code.
Deepfake was used for this video.
Looks like Siu Zi-yiu is most probably dead.
Just think, why would someone on the run
who ghosted her own father,
regularly go live online?
Unless someone posed as her
and used her to harass Yau You-fong
and Man Nga-kei.
One other point can prove
Siu Zi-yiu is dead.
Look at these three dolls.
Siu Zi-yiu's father Siu Bong-chak mentioned
his daughter might have disappeared,
but the Kuman Thongs she worshipped
were left in the studio.
Those who believe in their power put
heavy emphasis on their worship.
Not feeding them regularly may result
in them biting back.
You mean even on the run,
she should have brought them with her?
Though we haven't located Siu Zi-yiu's body,
she has been missing for two weeks.
Plus there's blood found in her car...
Let's assume Siu Zi-yiu is dead,
her killer posed as her in the livestreaming
and harassed Man Nga-kei and Yau You-fong
to give the illusion Siu Zi-yiu
is still alive.
Someone who knows deepfake techniques
and how to hide the IP address in
sending messages,
the killer should be an I.T. expert.
Probably someone within Man Nga-kei
and Yau You-fong's social circle.
Those harassing messages
either call Yau You-fong a scumbag
or urge Man Nga-kei to leave her ex-husband.
The killer's motive is obviously jealousy.
It may be a woman romantically involved
with Yau You-fong.
Thinking back.
If the child bride is after you both,
it could be someone near you.
The prime suspect is someone connected
to me and Angie...
This is no time for jokes, you brat!
I wanted to know what happened
to Master Chow and Miss Koo
after they were married.
I also wanted to find more clues
on the child bride.
But maybe I was too nervous.
I couldn't get back into the hypnotic state.
Doing it once is quite impressive already.
Look at me, I couldn't do it at all.
If Sylvia is not the child bride,
let's go back to the walled village
and see if we could find other leads.
OK.
Auntie Mui said she has work to do.
Angie!
Don't touch or something bad would happen.
No. I won't let the child bride affect us
for the rest of our lives.
This key can't open any lock
in this mansion.
What is this key for?
The key fell from the wedding gown.
Maybe it belonged to the child bride.
Kwan Sir?
Bye!
What does Kwan Sir want?
He needs me down at the Police station.
Did they find Sylvia?
He didn't say. But he sounded anxious.
I'll drop you home first.
No need. I'll see what lock
can this key open.
Don't worry, I'm out in broad daylight.
I can look after myself.
I'll pick you up later.
Bye!
Miss Man, I found it! Follow me...
Over here...
I found a box.
The key opens this box.
It belonged to Master Chow?
Yes! You found the key,
you have affinity with him.
You should open it.
Mr. Yau, we asked you to come in
because we need you to provide information
about anyone romantically involved with you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
We're not interested in your personal life.
But based on the evidence and leads we have,
we believe the suspect's motive is jealousy.
Tell us about your exes, anyone you held
a torch for or who had a crush on you
or any one-night stands. Anything.
OK, that may take a while.
How about...among these...
anyone you find particularly suspicious?
Not really.
But the suspect sent out so many messages,
can't you track the IP address?
We're looking into that.
But the suspect is very clever,
every message and video
had multiple encryptions.
It'll take some time.
Unless the suspect goes live again.
Then it'll be easier to trace her.
Unfortunately, Siu Zi-yiu's channel
has been very quiet lately.
Does anyone you know have any small gestures
or any little habits?
I may remember if I see it.
I'll show you the recent footage from
Sylvia's channel.
See if that'll help.
Those of you born in the Year of the
Dragon, Dog and Rooster...
A cockroach!
Angie!
Davis? What did the Police want with you?
Nothing much. They showed me
Sylvia's old footage,
and asked me if I recognize any
characteristics of the suspect.
But I couldn't.
What about you? Anything?
You look terrible.
This tin box...
Auntie Mui gave it to me.
The key opens this tin box.
(New People Daily)
(Ruthless sorcerer killed and scammed money)
This is a newspaper from the
early days of the Republic.
It's a letter Master Chow sent
to the newspaper.
I read it and found out what happened
to Master Chow and Miss Koo
after they got married.
It's a letter Master Chow sent
to the newspaper.
I read it and found out what happened
to Master Chow and Miss Koo
after they got married.
Here...
Ning-yuk, how do you feel?
Kai-hin, I'm sorry!
I won't make it...
No! You'll be fine, Ning-yuk...No...
Master Chow...
Master Sin...
Why is Ning-yuk so seriously ill?
Is it because the weddings clashed?
Most probably.
I just got word,
soon after the child bride got married,
a fire broke out in her house
and her husband died in the fire.
What about Ning-yuk?
Please help her. Help Ning-yuk...
I can't live without her.
Master, don't worry!
I have a way to resolve this.
Really?
What are you doing here?
Master, you look terrible. How is Miss Koo?
You should talk. The clash you arranged
made Ning-yuk seriously ill.
How dare you show your face around here?
She took you from me.
You promised you'd marry me.
Have you forgotten your promise?
I was eight years old.
It was a child's talk.
How could you hold me to that?
Even if you think I let you down,
I never treated you unfairly over the years.
You like pretty clothes,
I tailor made any style for you.
I even found you a good husband
so you'll have no worries.
I even gave you a wedding gown.
Why did you come after us? Why?
I'm sorry, please forgive me.
I only wanted you to come back to me.
Ning-yuk is the only one I love.
No one can take her place.
I don't ever want to see you again.
Go away! Go...
Master...
Go away!
Open the door, Master, I'm sorry...Master...
You bloody monk, you scammed people
and broke up people's family.
If you dare save that tramp's life,
I will expose you.
Ning-yuk, how do you feel?
Ning-yuk, don't scare me.
Ning-yuk...no, Ning-yuk!
Help...
Look what you did to Miss Koo!
Master Chow won't change his mind.
Give it up.
Spare me your hypocrisy.
When Master was gravely ill
when he was little,
you told Madam Chow to buy a child bride
to bring him good luck.
You wanted to please Master Chow,
you deceived him with your fallacies
and told the Chow family I'll bring
bad lucky to the family
and asked them to marry me off.
My pathetic life is entirely your doing.
You were greedy enough
to suggest I clash the wedding
to hurt Koo Ning-yuk,
You have no right to tell me to stop.
You killed Ning-yuk...
Let me explain...
You're not welcome in this family.
You have no place in this village.
Get out! Get out!
I'm sorry, it was my fault...
Ning-yuk, don't worry.
You'll always be the only woman I love.
What about the child bride?
Did the newspaper mention any features
about her?
The story is about the monk.
His monastic name is Yiu-sin.
Master Chow was afraid he might
change his name
and continue to swindle other people.
That's why he emphasized the point
Yiu-sin casts a spell or conducts divination
with his left hand.
Yiu-sin? Left hand?
Well? Did you think of something?
Sylvia writes with her right hand.
But when she uses the pendulum,
or draws a tarot card
she uses her left hand.
They both have the word "Yiu"
in their names.
You mean Sylvia is not the reincarnation
of the child bride?
I'm not surprised.
That's why Sylvia conned me into
investing with her.
That made sense.
The child bride probably felt the monk
ruined her life
and she didn't get to marry Master Chow
in the end,
that's why she repeatedly harassed us
and killed Sylvia as well.
Her next step...
Angie, don't be afraid.
Though we don't know her next move,
at least we know she doesn't know any magic.
The Police will be monitoring the situation.
Don't get any ideas.
Give me your phone.
What for?
I installed a locator app.
We'll know where each other is.
If anything should happen,
I can find you at once and protect you.
Liz...I ordered hot lemon water for you.
Is that OK?
What do you want?
Angie said you have been sick for a while.
Just checking if you have recovered.
If you have time to care about other people,
why don't you clean up your mess?
You're quite right.
I have enough problems as it is.
Even if I want to protect Angie,
I can't be with her 24 hours a day.
I hope you can spend more time with her.
What do you mean by that?
The Police suspects Sylvia has been murdered
which means a killer has been
harassing me and Angie.
And we have no idea what the killer
will do next.
But...Sylvia has been posting and
livestreaming online.
Why would the Police think she's dead?
Sylvia's Dad reported her missing.
The Police started an investigation.
Since Sylvia's channel has been
quiet lately,
the Police feel if she was still alive,
she should continue to livestream
and have updates.
That's why they think she had been killed
and the killer is someone among us.
I told Angie to stay away from you.
OK, I'll keep an eye on her.
Liz, why are you biased against me?
Are you angry with me?
Or you have something else in mind?
You're worried you can't control yourself
that's why you're avoiding me.
What are you getting at?
I know what happened that night
had a big impact on you.
Are you angry about that?
Or you simply can't let it go?
Yau You-fong, who do you think you are?
A real charmer?
I was drunk and used you as a vibrator
the other night.
Give it a rest.
Excuse me...my name is Davis.
Can I borrow your phone.
My phone died and I wanted to get a ride.
Sure!
Thanks.
Your wallpaper...is that
a village in Lille in France?
Yes!
I was there.
It's a perfect place to paint and
find inspiration.
Hi!
Liz...Angie! Time for a break...
How attentive!
Look! He bought three...
He looks after you too.
That's better.
Let me do it...
Sure!
Look! There are three heads...
Really?
Tighten this one...OK! Done.
Amazing!
No wonder you're the designer. Good job!
Angie is my roommate.
You already show up all the time,
now you even put up a new bed.
When are you moving in?
Good idea...
Are you crazy? Don't say that!
Who said he can move in?
Why did you have a fight?
You should talk things out.
You know your bestie.
She doesn't tell you anything.
She holds everything in.
Sometimes, I'd rather she can be
more like you
and blurt everything out.
I wish my boyfriend would think like that.
It's just a cockroach.
It doesn't understand you raised your hands
to surrender.
I was scared.
It's gone, look!
You're quite cute.
Why did your boyfriend dump you?
He thinks I'm too outspoken and aggressive.
Aggressive?
Liz!
Angie...
I need to tell you something.
Really? I have something to tell you too.
You go first.
Davis just proposed!
Didn't you have a fight yesterday?
Yes, I was quite surprised myself.
He said precisely because we had a fight,
he was more certain about our love.
Congrats!
Mom, I'm home.
Mom!
Wow, you made such a mess.
Move over. Let me clean that up for you.
No...I'll do it myself.
OK, then I'll go shower.
I'm beat after a long day.
Hey...Angie told me
the Police summoned you for questioning.
Don't tell me they think you're the killer.
Of course not. They wanted me for leads.
Any progress?
I suspect Liz was posing as Sylvia.
Liz? Angie's bestie?
I'm not sure.
That's why I didn't tell Angie.
I only told the Police.
Liz is with Angie all the time.
Will Angie be in any danger?
That's why I'm anxious to find evidence.
I'm working with the Police
and I tried to get Liz to
resume livestreaming.
If she was posing as Sylvia,
the Police can track her down.
What? You're the bait?
Are you sure you're safe?
I'm just the backseat adviser.
The Police is doing all the work.
Don't worry about me.
Angie, you said the mattress
is uncomfortable.
This brand is quite good.
You should get one.
The one I have is still good.
No need to get a new one.
Of course not! You have back pain.
The mattress is the reason.
Come...let's look at this one.
It's suitably firm and very comfortable.
Come, sit down...
Sylvia is on live...
I have bad news for everyone.
Something bad happened to me lately
that had a big impact on me.
I want to go away for a while.
This channel will be suspended indefinitely.
Well? Did we track the location?
We need more time because of multiple VPNs.
Hurry...
Yau You-fong is quite resourceful
and made Siu Zi-yiu go live.
Is Siu Zi-yiu's imposter
really Man Nga-kei's friend Yip Lai-yan?
We managed to smoke her out,
we shouldn't come back empty handed.
Got it! Luk Fat Industrial Building
in Fo Tan.
The civet cat is in Luk Fat Industrial
Building in Fo Tan! Go!
Copy!
Why are you leaving?
I don't want to see you go.
I don't want to go either.
But all good things must come to an end.
It's almost time for me to go off air.
Can you draw a tarot card for us
for the last time?
OK, let's take a look at your fortune
for this month.
It's the Wheel of Fortune.
In reverse, it means
luck is not on our side.
Things around us are not within our control.
It's time we learn to let go
and take things as they come.
Police!
We think a suspect is livestreaming.
We need to search the premises.
Just remember, every cloud
has a silver lining,
when things hit rock bottom,
they will only get better.
OK, I must go now. See you around.
(End of livestreaming)
Calling control, the civet cat got away.
She got away.
Angie...
Why didn't you tell me you're working
with the Police?
You don't trust me?
I'm still guessing.
That's why I didn't tell you.
The Police said Sylvia's imposter
is an I.T. expert
who probably knows our whereabouts.
Who else could it be but Liz?
It can't be Liz.
She's my bestie. She would never hurt me.
That's how she can fool you...
It's not her. Definitely not!
You don't have to take my word for it.
Listen to the Police...
(Kwan Sir of the Crime Unit)
Kwan Sir?
We saw the CCTV
and confirmed Yip Lai-yan posed as
Sylvia in the livestreaming.
But she got away.
We're afraid she might strike back.
You must be careful.
OK, we will.
Why Liz?
(New People Daily)
(Ruthless sorcerer killed and scammed money)
I never treated you unfairly over the years.
You like pretty clothes,
I tailor made any style for you.
Hello, Liz? You finally called back.
Where are you?
I need to ask you something.
Let's meet somewhere.
This afternoon at 2 o'clock,
on the hillside of Chun Ming Mountain
in Tai Po,
the Police found a headless corpse
hidden inside a suitcase.
It has been confirmed that the deceased
was Siu Zi-yiu,
who has been reported missing.
According to the autopsy report,
though her fingerprints have been removed,
the medical examiner compared
the DNA of the body
with hair found in Siu Zi-yiu's studio
and found a perfect match
and confirmed the deceased was Siu Zi-yiu.
The estimated time of death
was two weeks ago.
Yip Lai-yan posed as Siu Zi-yiu
after she was dead.
She's now the prime suspect.
Then she should be the one harassing
Yau You-fong and Man Nga-kei.
The apparatus found inside the suitcase
carrying the body,
do they belong to Siu Zi-yiu?
In any case, let's catch Yip Lai-yan
and ask her.
The Police is conducting the investigation
as a crime of passion
and put out a warrant of arrest
for Yip Lai-yan.
The suspect is a computer programmer
and a video game live streamer.
Anyone with any information of the suspect
please contact the Police at once.
The number you have dialed
cannot be connected...
(No signal from device)
Did something happen to Angie?
Angie...
Why did you do it, Liz?
Yes...I slept with Davis.
But I was drunk, I acted on an impulse.
All along, I felt guilty towards you.
But what about him?
He proposed the very next day!
Where are you? Call me back.
(No signal from device)
He was a player, he felt guilty...
Let go!
Your marriage was a mistake.
No...
It was good you got a divorce.
But why go back to him?
It's not like that...
Only because you won't let go,
or else none of this would have happened.
Come with me...
Let go of me!
(No signal from device)
(Chung Hung Industrial Building)
Angie...
Angie, where are you? Angie?
Angie...no...
Angie...don't scare me...
Angie, are you OK? Angie, wake up...
Angie?
Davis? I...
Don't move! Take it easy.
It hasn't been easy to stop the bleeding.
Thirsty? Want some water?
No, I'm fine.
Fine?
Mr. Yau, we came to see Miss Man.
Kwan Sir!
Sir!
Miss Man, can we take your statement?
OK.
Who stabbed you?
Liz did.
Sir, where is she?
We're still looking for her.
Why did you contact her?
Didn't you know she's wanted by the Police?
No, I didn't.
I have been calling her.
But she never called back.
Until tonight, she suddenly called me.
I wanted to ask her many questions
so I asked her to meet me.
What happened?
When I saw her, I asked her
if she killed Sylvia.
She became very agitated.
So agitated...as if she wanted to
kill me too.
Did Yip Lai-yan admit she's the killer?
Yes.
She posted online certain compromising
materials about Sylvia
and Sylvia found out it was her.
Sylvia confronted her in her flat.
They got into a heated argument
and she killed Sylvia by mistake.
Why did she post those materials
about Siu Zi-yiu?
I didn't know at first.
It never dawned on me either,
but she admitted to me
she had a one-night stand with Davis.
After Davis and I were divorced,
she was hoping she could be with Davis.
But Davis soon got into a relationship
with Sylvia,
and she was pissed
because she didn't think Sylvia
was worthy of Davis.
Later when she found out
Sylvia tried to con money from Davis,
she wanted to expose Sylvia
so Davis would see Sylvia for who she was
and leave her.
But she killed Sylvia by mistake.
You were besties, why did you harass you?
She knew I'm not over Davis.
She wanted to scare me
so I would back off.
But she didn't realize what she did
actually brought Davis and I
closer than before.
She was unresolved and she told me
all the women around Davis...
must die.
(Night of the incident at 3:00 a.m.)
The industrial building we're visiting today
is allegedly a popular spot for suicide.
Allegedly, after four workers died,
no one used this building anymore.
There are exactly four of us!
That's spooky!
Bite your tongue!
Let's move on, OK?
Hurry up...
That completes our adventure today.
Wait, where's Wilson?
Did he go to the bathroom?
Let's go back and find him.
Wilson, where have you been?
Look!
What is it?
Wilson found the body first.
Someone reported outside
Chung Hung Industrial Building,
Yip Lai-yan's body was found.
Her left leg was broken.
All the evidence and witnesses
indicated Yip Lai-yan murdered Siu Zi-yiu.
We searched her flat
and found evidence of her using deepfake.
Her motive...she was jealous of Siu Zi-yiu
because she was Yau You-fong's girlfriend.
She posed as Siu Zi-yiu in livestreaming
to cover up her crime.
Probably also out of jealousy,
she continued to harass and threaten
Yau You-fong and Man Nga-kei.
Luckily, Yau You-fong recognized
Yip Lai-yan's small gesture
and worked with us to lure
Yip Lai-yan out.
She gave herself away and finally
killed herself to escape punishment.
Good job! Keep up the good work.
Send me the report later.
Got it...
Here...
Thanks, Brother Bo.
You bought this vajra to cast away
evil spirits?
To cast away evil spirits?
Of course! What's bothering you?
Never mind. The file is closed already.
You can always re-open it.
Even though you're in charge of the case,
it doesn't mean you must figure it out.
Just tell us about it. We're a team, OK?
That's right. Tell us...
We'll help you out...
We'll figure it out for you.
Let's drink to that, we all worked so hard.
Hey, Brother Bo!
How come you have a drumstick and we don't?
Looks like Brother Bo is the biggest
beneficiary of today's afternoon tea.
That's right.
Go grab something to eat before
the food is gone.
You should eat something.
If you're hungry, you can't think.
I think there's more than one killer.
Just think. Even after everything
Yip Lai-yan did,
Yau You-fong is not hers to claim.
Who stands to benefit the most?
Angie...I wish to apologize to you properly.
What happened between Liz and I
was because I was drunk.
There's nothing between us.
After what happened, I felt so guilty
because I knew I let you down.
Right then and there I knew
how much you mean to me.
I decided to devote myself to you.
That's why I proposed on the next day.
She's dead.
I don't intend to dwell on the past.
You'll forgive me?
Can we go back to our life before?
This...this is not the right time to
think about that.
I'm not angry with you.
It's just that...I just lost my best friend,
I don't know what to do.
I'm sorry.
My mind is made up.
I lost you once,
I won't lose you again.
Please marry me again.
I'll use the rest of my life
to look after you.
Didn't you say you want to go away?
You like Japan.
Let's go there and start over, OK?
Davis, I'm still very much in love with you.
But we have been through so much,
it's time we think things through properly.
I understand.
Your bestie was the killer
and she even tried to kill you.
That was such a major blow to you.
You suppose she was the child bride?
I thought about that when we met.
Auntie Mui gave me this sketchbook,
which I think belonged to Master Chow.
The drawings should be of the child bride.
She wore so many different clothes.
I did my research.
She came from an opera troupe.
After she was sold to the Chow family,
she occasionally performed in
different outfits.
That's very similar to cosplay.
I made sweet soup with eggs
and bean curd sheet.
Go get it from the kitchen.
OK.
How are things with you two?
Are you back together?
I think Davis loves me
and he has become more down to earth.
I might as well tell you.
I love him as much as I did before.
But after we've been through so much,
I can't decide what to do.
I'd love to have you as a daughter-in-law.
But I know my son too well.
He's not someone who can settle down.
I know. That's why I think...
You must think carefully.
I don't want to see you get hurt again, OK?
I know.
Hello? Is this the recycling company?
Yes, I have some furniture...
Can you come and take a look?